Guide to the Special events collection ARCH074
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
- Other Events, 1957-2018; IV
  - Magrucler, Jebstuart, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 13)
  - Parents Day Financial and Statistics, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 14)
  - Calder Financial, 1973 Oct 10 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 15)
  - Calder Lists, 1973 Oct 10 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 16)
  - Calder Arrangements, 1973 Oct 10 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 17)
  - Retirement Dinner, 1973 May 30 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 18)
  - Chinese Opera, 1973 Nov 18 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 19)
  - Hartt Opera Theater Extravaganza, 1973 Mar 17 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 20)
  - Heller, Joseph, 1973 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 21)
  - Charter Day, 1973 - 1976 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 22)
  - Corporate Social Responsibility, 1974 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 23)
  - Black Parents Day, 1974 Feb 23 (Box Other Events 7, Folder 24)
  - Abrahamason Medal Conferral, 1974 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 1)
  - Insights XI, 1974 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Insights I, 1974 Nov 07 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Lazar's Seminar, 1974 Nov 26 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 4)
  - Medal Conferral, 1974 Apr 24 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 5)
  - Parents Day, 1974 Oct 19 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 6)
  - Parents Day Financial, 1974 Oct 19 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 7)
  - Teacher' Insights II, 1975 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 8)
  - Lazar Seminar, 1975 Feb 04 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 9)
  - Pride's Second Anniversary, 1975 Apr 28 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 10)
  - Learning Lab Dedication, 1975 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 11)
  - Insights IV, 1975 Dec 03 (Box Other Events 8, Folder 12)
  - Teacher Insights, 1975 Nov 03 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 1)
  - Grasso, Ella Trambussi, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 2)
  - Art School Degree Ceremony, 1975 Feb 16 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 3)
  - H.A.S. Auxiliary Tour, 1975 May 12 - 17 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 4)
  - Beatman Series, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 5)
  - Beatman Lectures, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 6)
  - Devlin, Bernadette, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 7)
  - Guatemalan Affair, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 8)
  - Superintendent's Dinner, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 9)
  - Insights XII, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 10)
  - Insights XIII, 1975 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 11)
  - Hillyer Alumni Insights, 1976 Mar 06 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 12)
  - Bicentennial, 1976 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 13)
  - Lecture Art Collecting as a Social Habit, 1976 (Box Other Events 9, Folder 14)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, 1977 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 1)
  - White House Conference, 1978 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 2)
  - White House Conference Hartford Courant, 1978 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 3)
  - White House Briefing on Inflation, 1978 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 4)
  - Banner Year Donation Outreach, 1979 Jun (Box Other Events 10, Folder 5)
  - Private Higher Education in the 80's, 1980 May 18 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 6)
  - Islam in Ferment, 1980 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 7)
  - Ellsworth Lectures, 1980, 1995 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 8)
  - Goodman, Ellen, 1981 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 9)
  - Farrakhan, Louis, 1981 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 10)
  - Halberstam, David, 1981 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 11)
  - 25th Charter Anniversary, 1981 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 12)
  - Recognition Day, 1982 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 13)
  - Lectures, 1982 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 14)
  - Asimou, Isaac, 1982 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 15)
  - Economy Symposium, 1985 Oct 05 (Box Other Events 10, Folder 16)
  - Economy Symposium Transcription, 1985 Oct 05 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 1)
  - Visiting Lecture Series, 1985 Oct 17 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 2)
  - Charles W. & Ruth B. Deeds Symposium, 1985 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 3)
  - Deeds Symposium, 1985 - 1986 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Seaga Edward P.G., 1987 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 6)
  - Silber, John R., 1987 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 7)
  - National League of Baseball Diamond Club Dinner, 1987 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 8)
  - Bradley, ED, 1987 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 9)
  - Hart, Gary, 1987 - 1988 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 10)
  - HAS Koopman Chair, 1988 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 11)
  - Joseloff Gallery, 1988 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 12)
  - Tribute Martin Luther King Jr., 1989 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 13)
  - Inauguration Week, 1989 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 14)
  - University Day, 1989 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 15)
  - Ralph Nadar, 1989 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 16)
  - Distinguished Visiting Lecturers, 1990 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 17)
  - Tip O'Neill, 1990 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 18)
  - Reich, Robert B., 1991 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 19)
  - Jonathan Miller, 1992 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 20)
  - Tribute to Moshe Paranov, 1994 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 21)
  - Humanities Center, 1992 - 1996 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 22)
  - Library of Congress Bicentennial, 2000 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 23)
  - Holidays, 2000 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 24)
  - Rogow Distinguished Lecture Series, 2000 - 2012 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 25)
  - Queen Noor of Jordan, 2001 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 26)
  - Big Brother Big Sisters, 2001 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2002 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 28)
  - Distinguished Visiting Lectures Program, 2004 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 29)
  - Founders Planned Giving Society, 2005 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 30)
  - College of Engineering and Architecture, 2005 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 31)
  - Martin Luther King's Birthday, 2007 (Box Other Events 11, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2007 - 2008 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 1)
  - Martin Luther King, 2008 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2008 - 2009 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 3)
  - External Funding Recognition Reception, 2008 - 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 4)
  - Martin Luther King Birthday, 2009 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 5)
  - Community Day, 2009 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2009 - 2010 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 7)
  - Bill Clinton Visits University, 2010 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 8)
  - Martin Luther King Birthday, 2010 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2010 - 2011 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 10)
  - Recognition Day, 2010 - 2013 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 11)
  - Park Water Arts, 2011 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 12)
  - Hertford Lecture, 2011 - 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2011 - 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 14)
  - Thanksgiving Inter-Faith Service, 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 15)
  - Founders Day, 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 16)
  - Public Service Lecture, 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 17)
  - Hawktober Weekend, 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 18)
  - Land Exhibit "Lest We Forget", 2012 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2012 - 2013 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 20)
  - Martin Luther King Birthday, 2013 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 21)
  - President Barack Obama Visit, 2013 Apr; 1 Files legal size folder; 1 Files Oversize 20 x 24 folder Newspapers (Box Other Events 12, Box Shared Oversized 1)
  - Faculty Staff Kick Off, 2013 - 2014 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 23)
  - Recognition Day, 2014 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2014 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 25)
  - MLK Day, 2014 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2015 - 2017 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 27)
  - MLK Day, 2016 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 28)
  - Facilities Department Semi-Annual Recognition Ceremony, 2017 Jan 12 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 29)
  - MLK Day, 2017 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 30)
  - Board of Regents Dinner, 2017 Jun 15 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Staff Kickoff, 2017 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Showcase, 2017 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 33)
  - MLK Day, 2018 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 34)
  - Facilities Department Semi-Annual Recognition Ceremony, 2018 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 35)
  - Recognition Day, 2018 (Box Other Events 12, Folder 36)
- Photographs, 1957-2007; V
  Custodial History
  Some of the photographs in this collection were once part of the "Event Photographs Collection (ARCH107)" which were merged with this collection in 2018.
  - Commencement Photographs, 1957-2014
    - 1957 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 1)
    - 1958 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 2)
    - 1962 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 3)
    - 1963 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 4)
    - 1964 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 5)
    - 1965 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 6)
    - 1966 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 7)
    - 1968 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 8)
    - 1969 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 9)
    - 1970 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 10-11)
    - 1971 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 12)
    - 1972 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 13-14)
    - 1973 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 15-16)
    - 1976 (Box Photographs 1, Folder 17)
    - 1979 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - Circa 1970s (Box Photographs 2, Folder 1)
    - 1981 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 2)
    - 1986 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 3)
    - 1987 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 4)
    - 1988 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 5)
    - 2000 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - 2012 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - 2014 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - 2004-2007 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 5.5, DVD/CD Box 1)
      This file includes CDs of Hooding Ceremonies for 2004 and 2006, as well as thumbnails removed from DVD cases for the Educational Leadership Doctorate Hooding Ceremonies for 2006 and 2007. It also includes CDs of the Fall 2006, and Spring and Fall 2007 Commencement photographs.
    - undated (Box Photographs 2, Folder 6 - 7, Shared Photograph Box 2)
  - Other Event Photographs, 1958-2004
    - Campus Preview, 1958 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 8 - 11)
    - Contract Signing, 1958 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 12)
    - Inauguration, 1959 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 13)
    - Cavalcade of Progress U.S. Army, 1959 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 14)
    - Charter Day, 1959 - 1981 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 15)
    - Fleming, 1960 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 16)
    - Fleming Conference, 1960 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 17)
    - Bush, Prescott with A.S. Wilson, 1962 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 18)
    - Naval Research Award, 1963 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 19)
    - Open House, 1963 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 20)
    - Flagpole Dedication Navy Day Celebration, 1964 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 21)
    - U-Thant visit, 1968 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 22)
    - University Medal, 1969 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 23)
    - Gregory, Dick, 1969 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 24)
    - Teacher CORPS Banquet, 1969 (Box Photographs 2, Folder 25)
    - Awards Feldman, Rabbi Abraham and O'Brien, Archbishop, 1969 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 1)
    - Pearlman, Iztack, 1973 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 2)
    - Wicyer, Tom, 1973 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 3)
    - Charter Day, 1973 - 1976 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 4)
    - University Medal, 1977 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 5)
    - Iva Levine, Robert Yelliu, John Mrgavera, Davis Corfec, Richard Keller, 1982 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 6)
    - Operation Teamwork, 1984 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 7)
    - March of Dimes Walkathon, 1987 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 8)
    - Measles Shot, 1989 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 9)
    - Recognition Day, 1989 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified, 1990 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 11)
    - Race-car Paradise, 1990 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 12)
    - Pride Program, 1990 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 13)
    - Ellsworth Symposium, 1990 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 14)
    - Bowls, 1990 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 15)
    - Spring Fling, 1995; Circa 1990- circa 1999 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - Construction Institute Annual Reception, 1996 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 16)
    - Musical Performers, 1996 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - Fall Fest, 1997 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 17)
    - Spring Konover, 1997 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 18)
    - Concerts/Battle of the Bands, 1997 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - U of H Today, 1998 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 19)
    - All Faculty - Staff Kick Off, 1998 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 20)
    - Big E, 2000 (Shared Photograph Box 2)
    - Big Brothers Big Sisters, 2001 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 21)
    - Dr. Manuel Ayau, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 22)
    - Yung Wing Hartford High, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 23)
    - American Originals, 2004 (Box Photographs 3, Folder 24)
    - Charter Day, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 25)
    - Commons Ribbon Cutting, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 26)
    - Campus Scenes, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 27)
    - Downtown Center and Hartford Courant, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 28)
    - Hartford Scholastic Challenge, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 29)
    - Moving in Day, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 30)
    - Racecar, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 31)
    - Student tutors at Weaver and Fox Middle School Educational Main street, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 32)
    - Take Back the Night, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 33)
    - Tonkin Speaking, undated (Box Photographs 3, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box Shared Photograph Box 3)
- Recordings, 1957-2017; VI
  - Commencements and Hooding Ceremonies, 1958-2012
    - 1958, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1959, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1960, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1961, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1962, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1963, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1964, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1965, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1966, 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1968, 2 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
    - 1969
      - Commencement Audio, 1969; 6 Reels Pair of masters and a pair of duplicate copies, and a pair labelled "names of people receiving degrees" 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
      - Commencement Film, 1969 Jun 8; 1 Reels 16mm film, color, sound speed. Labelled with #563 16mm, 9.25 inch reel, 600ft; 1 Reels Unclear if this is a duplicate of the 600ft recording, or a second part of the event recording. 16mm film, color, sound speed. Labelled with #562 16mm, 10.5 inch reel, 700ft; 1 Reels Marked as a duplicate - unclear if it is a duplicate of the 600 or 700 ft recordings, or both. 16mm film, color, silent but sound speed. Labelled with #559 16mm, 10.5 inch reel, 700ft (Reel 0207303177043, Reel 0207303177050, Reel 0207303177068)
    - 1970
      - Commencement Audio, 1970; 2 Reels Two part recording 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
      - Commencement Film, 1970 Jun 7; 1 Reels 16mm, color, silent (but at sound speed). Was labelled #573 16mm, 12.5in reel (Reel 0207303177118)
    - 1971
      - Commencement Audio, 1971; 3 Reels Reels #1 and #2 and unnumbered 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
      - Commencement Film, 1971 June 6; 1 Reels 16mm film, Color, sound speed, running time 20 min. 16mm, 10.5 in reel (Reel 0207303177035)
    - 1972
      - Commencement Audio, 1972; 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
      - Commencement Film, 1972 May 27; 1 Reels Master copy color, silent but sound speed, 20 min. 16mm film, on 13.75in reel (film does not fill reel, only about 9in wide).; 2 Reels Duplicate copies 16mm film, color, silent, but sound speed. Labelled as #560 and #561 (copy) 16mm, 10.5in. reel (Reel 0207303177092, Reel 0207303177076, Reel 0207303177084)
    - 1973
      - 1973 Jun 3; 2:00PM, 1 Cassettes (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the College of Arts and Sciences and Hartt College which occurred at 2:00PM on June 3, 1973.
      - 1973 Jun 3; 10:30AM, 2 Cassettes In two parts on one side of two cassette tapes. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the Commencement program for the College of Education and the Hartford Art School.
      - 1973 Jun 3; 5:00PM, 2 Cassettes In two parts on one side of two cassette tapes. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the College of Basic Studies, Ward Technical College, the College of Engineering, and the Austin Dunham Barney School of Business and Public Administration.
      - 1973 Jun 3, 1 Cassettes One side of a cassette tape. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the honorary degree receipients Robert Lee Steele, Constance Baker Motley, and Reverand James Fairfield English, Jr.
    - 1974
      - 1974 Jun 2; 10:30AM, 1 Cassettes One side of one cassette tape. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        The recording is of the University's 10:30AM commencement with honorary degree recipient Olcott Damon Smith.
      - 1974 Jun 2; 2:00PM, 1 Cassettes One side of one cassette tape. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        The recording is of the University's 2:00PAM commencement with honorary degree recipients Felix A. Babel and Ruth A. Haas.
      - 1974 Jun 2; 5:00PM, 1 Cassettes One side of one cassette tape. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        The recording is of the University's 5:00PM commencement with honorary degree recipients Hugh Meade Alcorn, Jr. and John Moran Bailey.
    - 1975
      - 1975 Jun 1; 10:30AM, 1 Cassettes One cassette recorded on both sides. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the Samuel I. Ward Technical College, College of Arts and Sciences, and Hartt College of Music which occurred at 10:30AM on June 1, 1975.
      - 1975 Jun 1; 2:00PM, 1 Cassettes Recorded on one side of one casette. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the 1975 commencement for the College of Engineering, Austin Dunham Barney School of Business and Public Administration, and Hartford Art School which occurred at 2:00PM on June 1, 1975.
      - 1975 Jun 1; 5:00PM, 1 Cassettes One side of one cassette tape. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the College of Basic Studies Division of Secretarial Science and the College of Education which occurred at 5:00PM on June 1, 1975.
    - 1976
      - 1976 May 30; 10:30AM, 1 Cassettes (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the College of Basic Studies, Austin Dunham Barney School of Business and Public Administration, and College of Engineering which occurred at 10:30AM on May 30, 1976.
      - 1976 May 30; 2:00PM, 1 Cassettes (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the Samuel I. Ward Technical College, College of Arts and Sciences, and Hartford Art School which occurred at 2:00PM on May 30, 1976.
      - 1976 May 30; 5:00PM, 1 Cassettes (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the College of Education and Hartt College of Music which occurred at 5:00PM on May 30, 1976.
    - 1977
      - 1977 Jun 5; 10:30AM, 2 Cassettes Two copies of a one tape recording. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the Hartford Art School, College of Arts and Sciences, and College of Engineering which occurred at 10:30AM on June 5, 1977.
      - 1977 Jun 5; 2:00PM, 2 Cassettes Two copies of a one tape recording. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the College of Basic Studies, College of Education and Allied Services, and Samuel I. Ward Technical College which occurred at 2:00PM on June 5, 1977.
      - 1977 Jun 5; 5:00PM, 2 Cassettes Two copies of a one tape recording. (Box Cassette Box 1)
        This recording is of the commencement program for the Austin Dunham Barney School of Business and Public Administration and the Hartt College of Music which occurred at 5:00PM on June 5, 1977.
    - 1978
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1978 Jun 4; 2 Reels Two part recording 7 inch; 2 Cassettes One is marked "Master" and the other "copy" (Box Audio Reels 1, Box Cassette Box 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video, 1978 Jun 8; 2 Cassettes U-matic, recorded in two parts (Box U-matic 1)
      - Commencement Film, 1978; 2 Reels color, silent but sound speed. Unclear if reels are duplicates are two parts of a single event. 16mm, 7in reel (Reel 0207303177019, Reel 0207303177027)
    - 1979
      - Commencement Audio, 1979; 1 Reels 7 inch (Box Audio Reels 1)
      - University of Hartford Commencement Video Tape 1, 1979 May 20; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 1)
      - University of Hartford Commencement Video Tape 2, 1979 May 20; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 1)
      - University of Hartford Commencement Video Tape 3, 1979 May 20; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 1)
      - University of Hartford Commencement Video Tape 4, 1979 May 20; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 1)
    - 1980
      - 1980, 2 Reels 7 inch; 1 Reels 5 inch; 3 Cassettes Appear to be two sided and could be identical to each other.. (Box Audio Reels 1, Box Cassette Box 1)
    - 1981
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1981; 1 Reels 7 inch; 1 Cassettes (Box Audio Reels 1, Box Cassette Box 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video, 1981; 2 Cassettes U-matic; two part recording (Box U-matic 1)
    - 1982
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1982 May 16; 2 Cassettes Appear to be duplicates of each other. (Box Cassette Box 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 5, 1982; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 6, 1982; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 7, 1982; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 8, 1982; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 9, 1982; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video, 1982; 1 Cassettes U-matic; Label on the actual tape is "WTNH-TV New Haven; Action News; Sunday, May 23, 1982; 7PM" [It is unclear if this label is accurate]. (Box U-matic 2)
    - 1983
    - 1984
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1984 May 13; 1 Cassettes (Box Cassette Box 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation, 1984; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
    - 1985
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1985 May 19; 2 Cassettes Unclear if it is a two part recording, or duplicates. They are labelled "Tape 1" and "Tape 2." (Box Cassette Box 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video, 1985 May 19; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
    - 1986 May 18, 1 Cassettes; 1 Cassettes VHS (Box Cassette Box 1, Box VHS Box 1)
    - 1987 May 17, 2 Cassettes Unclear if it is a two part recording or duplicates. One is labeled "Commencement, Arts and Sciences Ceremony" and the other reads "Commencement."; 1 Cassettes VHS (Box Cassette Box 1, Box VHS Box 1)
    - 1988
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1988 May 15; 1 Cassettes (Box Cassette Box 1)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 1, 1988 May 15; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 2, 1988 May 15; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 3, 1988 May 15; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video, 1988 May 15; 1 Cassettes VHS - unconfirmed, but likely a duplicate copy from U-matic tapes (Box VHS Box 1)
    - 1989
      - University of Hartford Graduation Audio, 1989 May 14; 2 Cassettes Unclear if the recording is in two parts, or if they are duplicates. One is labelled "Tonkin Commencement" and the other is just "Commencement." (Box Cassette Box 2)
      - University of Hartford Graduation Video Tape 1, 1989 May 14; 1 Cassettes U-matic (Box U-matic 3)